<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Talking Isn't Everything</name>
    <author>cyanobot</author>
    <packageId>cyanobot.TalkingIsntEverything</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <description>This mod aims to make an inability to talk less crippling. A number toggleable options are provided to control what mute pawns can and can't do.\n\nA pawn is "mute" if they are incapable of Talking (Talking 0% in the Health tab), whether that's due a genetic inability, injury, or any other reason. (Mute is not the same as Incapable of Social work - this mod does not change anything about pawns Incapable of Social.)\n\nFeatures:\n- New and adjusted log entries : The log will no longer describe mute pawns responding verbally to chit-chat, telling stories to babies, etc, etc.\n- (Toggleable) Animal interactions : Talking is no longer required to tame or train animals.\n- (Toggleable) Casual interactions : Allows mute pawns to maintain (or destroy) their social relationships using the same mechanics as any other pawn, but with new non-verbal log entries.\n- (Toggleable) Romance : Mute pawns can initiate romance and propose marriage instead of waiting for their partner to do so.\n- (Toggleable) Recruiting: Allows mute pawns to recruit prisoners to the colony.\n- (Toggleable) Slavery: Allows mute pawns to enslave prisoners and suppress slaves.\n- (Toggleable) Conversion: Allows mute pawns to use conversion interactions, abilities and rituals.\n- (Toggleable) Trials: Allows mute pawns to use the Trial leader ability.\n- (Toggleable) Speeches: Allows mute pawns to use Leader Speech and/or Throne Speech.\n- (Toggleable) Teaching: Allows mute pawns to teach Biotech children at the school desk.\n\nRegardless of enabled interactions, mute pawns will still have a very low Social Impact and Negotiation ability on account of their inability to talk.</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
	</loadAfter>	

</ModMetaData>